So hey guys, today we will join poster colours again,
first of all you guys should
wet your drawing sheet completely,
after that you guys have to spread the green colour in
this manner, after that you have to
fail the administration in the remaining area
and all the stocks should be in the same direction,
for Congress I have come Blue Mathura
Blackmail, in the last you guys have to
take white colour, apply it in the middle of these screens,
this will be your highlighted
area, to make stars I am
using a brush, you can add footry on one side, on the
opposite side of this track you guys
can make a free planet to
balance the printing, so guys if you
like the video then please like it and if you are
new to the channel then subscribe, we will meet
in the next video, till then bye